Kheel, Theodore W. Speeches and Articles 6021/005
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Interim Standards for Prepaid Legal Service Plans (Box 3, Folder 41)
- The International Teamster, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  April
- Interplay, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Interplay, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Interplay, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Invitation to 1964-1965 Forum Series of National Conference of Christians and Jews (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Is the Senate Obsolete as a Union Weapon? US News and World Report, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  June 25
- ITU In Crisis - Printers Must Organize (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Jackson, Samuel C. A New Center for Dispute Settlements (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Jackson, Schuyler E. Theodore W Kheel Prescribes Top-level Mediation Spokes, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  May 7
- Jacobs, Arnold S. The Impact of Securities Exchange Act. Cornell Law Review, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Janeway, Eliot. Is Business Cycle Old Hat? The Iron Age, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  March 1
- The Jewish Theological Seminary of America. The Institute for Religious and Social Studies (Box 4, Folder 11)
- A Job for Mr. Mitchell The Nation, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  Aug 2
- John Herling's Labor Letter, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  Dec 14
- John Herling's Labor Letter, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  Oct 25
- Kahn, Rodger. On the Brink of chaos. Saturday Evening Post, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Kahn-Freud, O Some Comments on Arbitration in the British Public Service (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Kaiser, Robert G. The Strike at the Washington Post (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Kaufman, Jacob J. and Patricia E. Flanary. The Effect of CB on the Issue of Excellence (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Kelber, Harry. A Proposal for a one-year Study of the Impact of Computers (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Kelber, Harry Chapter One: In Defense of CB and the Strike (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Kelber, Harry. The Response of NY Typographical Union no. 6 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Kelly, E.P. Jr. Academic CB: A Discussion of Some of the Advantages and Disadvantages (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Kelley, Edward (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Kelley, Grace E. Analysis of Legislation in 23 States Enabling CB (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Kelly, Matthew A. Collective Bargaining Reaffirmed (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Kennedy, Bruce F. Labor-Antitrust CB and The Competitive Economy (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Kerr, Clark and Lloyd Fischer. Conflict on the Waterfront (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Kheel, [Ann or Theodore W] Untitled Article for Herald Tribune, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  March 3
- Kheel, Ann S. Magazine Article #1, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Kheel, Ann S. Magazine Article #2, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Kheel: The Artist as Optimist. Newsweek, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  July 12
- Kheel, Ann S. Untitled Article for Riverdale Press, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  march
- Kheel, Theodore W. 20 Cent Fare Inevitable After Next July 1, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  Oct 3
- Kheel, Theodore W. A Balanced System of Transportation is a must, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  Dec 16
- Kheel, Theodore W. A Fare Question: The Issue the Candidates Don't Discuss NY Mag, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  April 23
- Kheel, Theodore W. A Large Apparel company Southeast US (Case study) (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Kheel, Theodore W. A Matter of Principle - A Study in Arbitration CT Federationist, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Kheel, Theodore W. A New Nation Emerges Herald Tribune, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  March 6
- Kheel, Theodore W. A Plan for Labor-Management Peace in NYC, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  Oct 19
- A Plan of Survival for Mass Transportation in New York City, Yonker, Newark, Jersey City and surrounding Areas. Report to Mayor Lindsay, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  Sept 17
- Kheel, Theodore W. A Transit Balance Sheet. The NY Times, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  March 17
- Kheel, Theodore W. American tobacco Co. NY, NY (Case Study) (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Kheel, Theodore W. An Analysis of the Tri-State Regional planning, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Keel, Theodore W. An Answer to Strikes Ag. The Public, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Arbitrators: Blessed or Damned? The Iron Age, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  Dec 20
- Kheel, Theodore W. Building First, Planning Later. The Village Voice, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  April 26
- Kheel, Theodore W. Bust the Trust (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Can We Stand Strikes by Teachers, PoliceReader's Digest, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  Aug.
- Kheel, Theodore W. Chapter 3 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Chapter 4 - State and Local Fair Employment Laws (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Ch. 5 Affirmative Action (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Ch. 6 How to Meet Problems Arising in the Workforce (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Ch. 7 Discriminating Practices in Unions and Apprenticeship (Box 4, Folder 53)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Ch8 Eleven Case Studies (Box 4, Folder 54)
- Kheel, Theodore W. (Band Community Disputes Monthly Labor Review, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Column for Victor Riesel, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  Jun 2
- Kheel, Theodore W. Conclusions (Box 4, Folder 57)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Continuation of Column for victor Riesel, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  June 9
- Kheel, Theodore W. Controversy over Union's Demand for the 40-hour Week on the Private Lines (Box 4, Folder 59)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Double the Bridge and Tunnel tolls, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  Aug 31
- Kheel, Theodore W. End to Ship labor Disputes SeenJournal of Commerce, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  May 22-28
- Kheel, Theodore W. Fact Sheet Section 6606: A Most Peculiar Law, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  Aug. 27
- Kheel, Theodore W. The Fight for a Transportation System That Works, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 63)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Ghana Puts Freedom in African Air. NY Herald Tribune, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  March 10
- Kheel, Theodore W. Gold Coast Becomes Democracy This Week. Herald Tribune, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  March 5
- Kheel, Theodore W. Hard Truths about Transit financing, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 66)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Chapter 2 - The Federal Fair Employment Practices (Box 4, Folder 67)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Has the Leopard Changed its Spots, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 68)
- Kheel, Theodore W. How Race Relations Affect Your Business (Ch. 1) (Box 4, Folder 69)
- Kheel, Theodore W. How Race Relations Affect Your business. Labor report bulletin, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  Aug. 15
- Kheel, Theodore W. How the Port Authority is Strangling New York, NY, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 71)
- Kheel, Theodore W. How the Steel Settlement Affects Other Industries Prentice Hall Info, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 72)
- Kheel, Theodore W. How to Get the Port Authority Buck on the Track, NY Mag, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  June 26
- Kheel, Theodore W. How to Handle Problems of Integrating Your Workforce Prentice-Hall, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  Nov 14
- Kheel, Theodore W. How to Mediate a Labor Dispute, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 75)
- Kheel, Theodore W. How to Prevent Strikes by the Public Employees, 1960-1968 (Box 4, Folder 76)
- Kheel, Theodore W. How to Stop Cars from Crushing the city New York, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  Sept 22
- Kheel, Theodore W. Hughes Aircraft Company Culver City, CA (Case Study) (Box 4, Folder 78)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Impact of Automation on CB and Vice Versa, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  Feb 26
- Kheel, Theodore W. In Defense of the Port Authority Bands, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Ingaus Shipbuilding corp. Pascagada, Mississippi (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Intro (Preface) (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Is a Negotiated Peace Possible interplay, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Is Imitation the Sincerest form of Flattery, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  Oct 26
- Kheel, Theodore W. Is the Strike Outmoded? (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Kheel, Theodore W. A Labor Policy for 1964 Personnel Journal April (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Labor trends in the Office and Clerical Fields Talk, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  Jan 22
- Kheel, Theodore W. Louisville and Washville RR Co. (Case Study) (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Management and Labor Leaders as Impartial Mediators The conference Board (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Manhattan Shirt co. New York, NY (Case Study) (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Mass Transit No Threats to Port Authority Bonds NY Law Journal, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  May 28
- Kheel, Theodore W. Memorandum on the Formulation and Finance of a Sound Transportation, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  Dec 9
- Kheel, Theodore W. Mobil Oil Co. Beaumont, TX (Case Study) (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Kheel, Theodore W. More People are Being Induced to Drive their OwnS6A, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Kheel, Theodore W. NY Herald Tribune Book Review of Organized Labor, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  Aug 10
- Kheel, Theodore W. NY Herald tribune Book Review of the State of the Unions, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Otis Elevator Co. New York, NY (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Points for consideration by the Governor's conference, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  Oct 11
- Kheel, Theodore W. Public Employee Unions Today, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  Nov 4
- Kheel, Theodore W. Reader's digest Article Intro, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  March 31
- Kheel, Theodore W. Report on Govt Program Ag. Discrimination Labor Report Bulletin, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  Aug. 30
- Kheel, Theodore W. Report to the Dept. of Transportation CB and Mass Transit Subsidies, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Revised Draft of Theodore Kheel Intro (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Rocking the Boat, Not Sinking H. The Sunday Herald Tribune Book Week, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Role of CB in Community conflict, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  Nov 12
- Kheel, Theodore W. Some Observations By Theodore W. Kheel on the Port of NY Authority, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Some Observations, Mainly Historical, On CB in the City Service (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Speech before the NY Society of Security The Wall Street Transcript, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  Jan 13
- Kheel, Theodore W. State Comptroller Arther Levitt Strikes Gold, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  Jan 12
- Kheel, Theodore W. Statement of Theodore W. Kheel for Publication in Riverdale Press, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  Aug 15
- Kheel, Theodore W. Strike is here to Stay, Says Mediator, TS and NY Mirror, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Strikes and Public Employment, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  Dec 19
- Kheel, Theodore W. Taylor Law Article - Syracuse Law Review, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Kheel, Theodore W. The Attack on CB Lithopinion, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Kheel, Theodore W. The Changing Patterns of CB in the US Under the Impact of Automation, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Kheel, Theodore W. The City Politic How to get a Billion Dollars New York, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  Feb 1
- Kheel, Theodore W. The City Public: Driving the Villains out New York, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  Sept 14
- Kheel, Theodore W. The Dynamics of the Steel Negotiations Lawyer's Weekly Report, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Kheel, Theodore W. The fight for a Transportation System that Works Lithopinion, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  Summer
- Kheel, Theodore W. The Impact of Automation and Technological Changes Denmark, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Kheel, Theodore W. The Legal Realities of the Bond Issue (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Kheel, Theodore W. The Machine Necessary to settle Seagoing Labor Problems, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  May 10
- Kheel, Theodore W. The Myopia of Technique (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Kheel, Theodore W. The Role of Arbitration in Labor Disputes NY Times Magazine, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  Jan 20
- Keel, Theodore W. The Self-sustaining Fare is Self Defeating, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Kheel, Theodore W. The Taylor Law: A Critical Examination Syracuse Law Review, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Theodore W. Kheel, President Authority for Coordinating Transportation, Inc., 1974 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  march 14
- Kheel, Theodore W. The Did not Fully Understand the Techniques In a Very Short Time (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Victor Riesel: Inside Labor The NY Journal America, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  July 9
- Kheel, Theodore W. Wage and Salary Stabilization Manpower Policies, wage and Salary Stabilization Controllers Inst., 1943 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Weirton Steel Co. Weirton, WV (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Western Electric co. NY, NY (Box 5, Folder 54)
- Kheel, Theodore W. What future for the Industrial Relations bill? The Times Business Week (Box 5, Folder 55)
- Kheel, Theodore W. What the New Labor Law Means to Mgmt., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 56)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Who's Fat Cat Now? The Sunday Herald Tribune Book Week, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  Oct. 27
- Kheel, Theodore W. Why an Institute of Collective Bargaining and Group Relations (Box 5, Folder 58)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Why the 2.5 Billion Dollar Transportation Capital Facilities Bond Act, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  Sept 28
- Kheel, Theodore W. Will Success foil the Port Authority, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  Oct 23
- Kheel, Theodore W. An Analogy for Race Relations; Address Accepting the Presidency, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  Sept 7
- Kheel, Theodore W. Complete Texts of Advisory Recommendations of Theodore W. Kheel Local 100 TWU (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Editorial Barron's, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  May
- Kheel, Theodore W. Editorial New York Times, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Guest Column for Publication Publishers-Hall Syndicate, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Guest Column for Publication in Publishers-Hall Syndicate, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  June 30
- Kheel, Theodore W. Guest Column for Publication in Publishers-Hall Syndicate, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  June 7
- Kheel, Theodore W. Guest Column for Publication in Publishers-Hall Syndicate, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Jan 3
- Kheel, Theodore W. How to Arbitrate a Labor Dispute, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Letter to Gael Greene, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Sept 21
- Kheel, Theodore W. Letter. Bamon's, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  May 13
- Kheel, Theodore W. Forward (Intro) Newspaper Strikes (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Racial Discrimination in Employment (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Reply Letter to Gael Greene New York, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  Oct 5
- (empty) (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Report of Findings and Recommendations Submitted to Mayor Robert F. (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Report to the Dept. of Transportation on CB and Mass Transit Subsidies (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Report to Vice President Johnson on the Structure and Operations (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Kheel, Theodore W. The Pros and cons of Compulsory Arbitration (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Blessed or Damned the Role of the Arbitrator in Modern Ind. Relations, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Draft Intro to Kelber and Schlesinger Book (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Kheel, Theodore W. How to Prevent Strikes by Teachers, Corps, Garbage Men and 200 Keepers (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Kheel, Theodore W. and Ann S Kheel Article for this Week This Week, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Kheel, Theodore W. and Cornelia Wyatt The Development of CB from Conspiracy, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Kheel, Theodore W. and JK Turcott. Transit and Arbitration A Decade of Decisions, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Kheel, Theodore W. and Larry Gage. Port Authority Book Outline (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Kheel, Theodore W. and Lewis B Kaden CB in Hospitals: A Plan to Resolve Impasses (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Kheel, Theodore W. and Lewis B Kaden Strike: For or Against, CB, Strikes, and the Legal Process (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Kheel, Theodore W. and Lewis B Kaden. Drafting of a Labor Agreement in an Inflation Economy, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Kheel, Theodore W. and Lewis B Kaden The Practical Limits of Arbitration In the Settlements of CB, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Kheel, Theodore W. and Lewis B Kaden The Practical and Robert J Kheel The Port Authority 1962 Covenant-Bar to Mass Transportation, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Kheel, Theodore W. and Rudolf Flesch. Plain Talk for the Rank and File. Union Contracts (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Kheel, Theodore W., Menoin Lewis, et al. Compulsory Arbitration in Disputes Affecting National Health and Safety (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Kheel, Theodore W., Paul W. Guthrie, et al. Report to the President by the Emergency Board E0 11006 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Killingsworth, Charles C Should CB be Revamped? Emergency Disputes Monthly Labor Review, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- King, Joe. Mass Transit Reuium or Revival?, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- The Kiplinger Washington Editors. Letter to Businessmen, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  Dec 18
- Kleiman (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Kluncker (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Knee (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Kramer (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Labor That 25 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Labor Arbitration Series: A Symposium Review. Stanford Law Review. July, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Labor Law Forum (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Labors Legal services (Box 6, Folder 44)
- Laborers Local 423 Legal (Box 6, Folder 45)
- Larson, Lex (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Lavalle (Box 6, Folder 47)
- Lawrence, Steven (Box 6, Folder 48)
- League Program to Beatrice Kheel. Printing News (Box 6, Folder 49)
- Leavens, John (Box 6, Folder 50)
- Lefkowitz (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Legal Assistance (Box 6, Folder 52)
- Legal Services (Box 6, Folder 53)
- Levinson, Harold (Box 6, Folder 54)
- Levinson, Herald (Box 6, Folder 55)
- Lieberman (Box 6, Folder 56)
- Livernash (Box 6, Folder 57)
- LMRS (Box 6, Folder 58)
- Local 423 (Box 6, Folder 59)
- Loveridge, Ray (Box 6, Folder 60)
- Lozier, Greg (Box 6, Folder 61)
- Theman They Call (Box 6, Folder 62)
- Managing Changes (Box 6, Folder 63)
- Marshall, Lawrence G (Box 6, Folder 64)
- Master Development Plan (Box 6, Folder 65)
- The Master Locksmith (Box 6, Folder 66)
- Maxwell Review (Box 6, Folder 67)
- McPherson, William (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Manon Support (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Men and Machines (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Merger of Taurus comm. w/ VPC Corp. (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Meyers, Frederic (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Moore, Gary and Randy, Elkin L and the Econ, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Morris, Charles (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Mortimer, Kenneth and Naomi Ross (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Murphy, Philip J Prepaid (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Murphy, Philips A Primer (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Murphy, William P. Theodore St. Antoine (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Murray, Thomas J. (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Nat Assn. of Broadcasters (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Not committee for Support (Box 7, Folder 14)
- National Consumer Center (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Nat. Electrical Center (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Nat Inst. Of Pub Affairs (Box 7, Folder 17)
- New England Council (Box 7, Folder 18)
- NJ State Bar (Box 7, Folder 19)
- New School Bulletin (Box 7, Folder 20)
- NY, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  April 6
- NY, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  June 8
- NY City Collison (Box 7, Folder 23)
- NY Bar Newsletter (Box 7, Folder 24)
- NY Transp. Bond Issue, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- NY Urban Dev. (Box 7, Folder 26)
- NY State Office State Comptroller 4th Branch (Box 7, Folder 27)
- NY State Office State Comptroller Indiv. (Box 7, Folder 28)
- NY State on Collective (Box 7, Folder 29)
- NY Sunday (Box 7, Folder 30)
- NY Type (Box 7, Folder 31)
- NYU Beyond Stut (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Nielson, Robert M. Corp. Mgmt. AFT (Box 7, Folder 33)
- New Yorker and Other Magazines (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Fortune, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Nineteen Seventy - Three Annual Survey of American Law pp566-575 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- 19th Annual (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Of Ships (Box 7, Folder 38)
- NYU Conference on Labor and Group Plan (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Page, Clint CATV: Two-way Across to City Hall (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Paul, Pope VI "The Development of People" (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Pay Structure Study: Railroad Operating Employees (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Pennsylvania State University Inst for Research on Human Resources. The Impact of CB (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Pertberg, A., B. Mannheim, G. Shall, and E. Rosenstein. The Recruitment, Development and Utilization (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Personnel Journal, 1963-1964 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- The Port Authority Commerce Building, Inland terminal No. 1 Extension of Lease (Box 8, Folder 7)
- The Port of New York Authority 4th Annual Report (Box 8, Folder 8)
- The Port of New York Authority 10th Annual Report (Box 8, Folder 9)
- The Port of New York Authority 11th Annual Report (Box 8, Folder 10)
- The Port of New York Authority 12th Annual Report (Box 8, Folder 11)
- The Port of New York Authority 25th Annual Report (Box 8, Folder 12)
- The Port of New York Authority 13th Annual Report (Box 8, Folder 13)
- The Port of New York Authority 15th Annual Report (Box 8, Folder 14)
- The Port of New York Authority 17th Annual Report (Box 8, Folder 15)
- The Port of New York Authority 21st Annual Report (Box 8, Folder 16)
- The Port of New York Authority 21st Annual Report (Box 8, Folder 17)
- The Port of New York Authority 22nd Annual Report (Box 8, Folder 18)
- The Port of New York Authority 23rd Annual Report (Box 8, Folder 19)
- The Port of New York Authority 26th Annual Report (Box 8, Folder 20)
- The Port of New York Authority 34th Annual Report (Box 8, Folder 21)
- The Port of New York Authority 34th Annual Report (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Prentice-Hall Practicing Attorney's Letter, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Prentice-Hall Practicing Attorney's Letter, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  April 12
- Prentice-Hall Practicing Attorney's Letter, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  June 21
- Prentice-Hall Practicing Attorney's Letter, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  May 24
- Prentice Hall Practicing Attorney's Letter, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Prentice-Hall Practicing Attorney's Letter, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Prepaid Legal Services: The Resources Center for Consumers of Legal Services (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Prison Grievance Procedures Corrections Magazines, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  Jan/Feb
- The Problems of Crisis Bargaining Program of Conference of the Labor-Management Dept. Manhattan College (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Program for Connecticut Attorney's Conference, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  March 19
- Program for the National Society of Fund Raising Executive International Conference on Philanthropy (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Program for the Forty-Ninth Annual Meeting National Industrial Council (Box 8, Folder 34)
- The Progressive, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Proposed Official Statement Dated June 9, 1975: The Port Authority of New York (Box 8, Folder 36)
- PA NY/NJ (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Public Personnel Administration Labor-Management Relations (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Public Report of Joint Printing Industry Board on the Selection of Apprentices (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Quelch, John A. and Paul W. Fams. Cases in Advertising and Promotion Management (Box 8, Folder 40)
- Cases in Advertising and Promotion Management (Box 8, Folder 41)
- The Racial Resolution in Advertising: A True Portrait of America (Box 8, Folder 42)
- Raskin, A.H. What Makes Teddy Kheel Run NY Times Mag, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  Dec 5
- Reader's Digest, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 44)
- Reapplication for Federal Planning Assistance Under the Public Telecommunications Facilities (Box 8, Folder 45)
- The Region's Agenda, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 46)
- Regulating the Political Activity Foundations Harvard Law Review, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 47)
- Reilly, James F. Study on the Financial Feasibility of the Proposed NYC Convention Center (Box 8, Folder 48)
- Remarks by Deputy Assistant Secretary of Labor Roukis Daily Labor Reporter, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 49)
- Draft - TWK Removing Obstacle to Automation, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  May 14
- Report of the Urban Development Task Force, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 51)
- Report to the Chairman of the Wage Stabilization Board by the Panel Considering Wage Stabilization (Box 8, Folder 52)
- Revising the New York City Charter: Intro Report (Box 8, Folder 53)